(Leonard:)I was reading about this jellyfish
that never dies.
(Leonard:)Instead it reverts to its asexual state
and then grows up again.
(Howard:)We thought my 90-year-old grandfather
had reverted to an asexual state...
(Howard:)...but the lawsuit from his Jamaican
caregiver proved us all wrong.
(Leonard:)My point is, immortality is not only
a possibility, it is real.
(Raj:)Only if you're this jellyfish,
which periodically...
(Raj:)...reverts to a mass
of undifferentiated protoplasm.
(Sheldon:)If I could keep my Gmail account,
I'd be okay with that.
- Hello, fellas.
- Hey, buddy.
- How are you?
- Remember we were trying to figure out...
...what that smell coming from
Professor Tupperman's office was?
(Leonard:)- Yeah.
- Turns out it was Tupperman.
(Barry:)Dead at his desk for two weeks.
(Howard:)- Terrible.
- Oh, my God.
In lieu of flowers,
the department chair is asking...
...that everyone donate a bottle
of Febreze.
(Sheldon:)If we're going to change the topic
from jellyfish...
(Sheldon:)...I'd be okay with brine shrimp
or the history of the unicycle.
Show a little compassion. The man died.